Are you really going to cut it?
あのう　本当に切るんですか
What? You said that you wanted it cut.
だって　春が髪切りたいって言ったんじゃ
You said that drying it is a pain.
いい加減乾かすのが大変って
I did, but...
言いましたけど
暑くて うっとしいとも
You said that it's hot and muggy out,
and that this would make a good summer memory.
夏の思いに切りましょうとも
I'm sure I didn't say that.
いえ　そんなことは
お前らに切ってほしくて言ったわけじゃねえよ
He wasn't asking you to cut it.
Relax your shoulders.
ほーら　肩の力抜いて　もっと気楽に構えて　春ちゃん
Don't be so uptight, Shun-chan.
Actually, seeing you guys more relaxed than I am makes me nervous.
っていうか
僕より皆が気楽に構えてることに一番不安を覚えるというか
それでは　初め
Let's begin.
I look forward to working with you.
よろしくお願いします
Um, I appreciate the thought,
あのう　気持ちだけで
but just cut it a little bit, please.
ちょっとだけでいいですからね
ちょっと待ってください
Wait a minute!
Are you both cutting my hair?
なんか二人一緒切ってません
Don't worry. We have two pairs of scissors...
ご安心を　はさみは二つですが
僕たち心は一つです
...but our heart is one.
Are you sure you're not cutting too much, Yuutan?
ちょい切りすぎじゃねえ　悠太
This side's shorter now.
今度はこっちのほうがみじけえな
全然一つじゃないじゃないですか
You're not one at all!
俺に合わせてよ
You should do it my way.
Can't we do it my way for once?
偶には俺に合わせてよ
話し合いながら切り進めないでください
Please don't cut and talk at the same time!
It's hot out.
それにしても暑いな
Since it's so hot, let's just cut it all off!
この際だからバッサリ行こうぜ　バッサリ
Ah, but, I don't want it all off...
いや　僕バッサリ切るつもりは
おおいいじゃん　夏らしくて
Oh, that's a nice, summery style.
Cut more off! Cut it off!
もっと切って切って
Um, summer's almost over.
Actually, you can just stop now.
あの　夏はもう終わりますし
っていうか　もういいですから
Don't hold back.
遠慮しないで　こうするといい感じだな
This'll look good.
No, it won't!
よくないです
Careful! Stop moving!
動くな　危ないって
There's no way they're going to listen to you.
こいつらが言うこと聞くわけないだろう
In the unyielding sweltering heat,
our short summer was coming to an end.
こうして　茹だるような暑さが収まらないまま
僕たちの短い夏は終わろうとしていた
Oh.
"Oh?" What do you mean by "oh"?!
あってなんですか　あって
It's best if you just disregard that.
いや　気にしないほうが
Yuuki, you...
祐希 それは
What is it?!
それはなんですか
それは気にしないほうが
You shouldn't worry about it.
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
mattezu ni toozaketeita no wa atashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta kedo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听 バサラ     翻译 景寒筱    日校 慧慧
总校 有明の月     时间轴 葛蔓     压制 PHENOTYPE
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Jeez, I told you to only cut a little bit off.
もう　ちょっとでいいって言ったのに
僕短くするとテンパ爆発しちゃうのに　もう
If my hair's too short, it'll frizz like crazy.
Sheesh.
Come in.
はい
Oh, thanks for having us over!
どうも　お邪魔します
Hello.
こんにちは
My my, you really took a leap, didn't you?
まあ　ずいぶん思い切ったわね
中学校の時以来
You haven't looked like that since middle school.
春ちゃん中学校までは髪短かったんだ
Shun-chan, you kept your hair short till middle school?
はい　でもその時も頭くりんくりんで
Ah, yes,
but it was really curly back then too.
むちゃくちゃ可愛かったんだろうな
I bet you were one cute middle-schooler, Shun-chan.
中学校時代の春ちゃん
Is your summer homework coming along well?
どう　夏休みの宿題捗ってる
Of course, since we have Kaname-kun's notes--
そりゃはもう　要君のノートが
Y-Yes, Kaname-kun's a fantastic teacher.
はい　要君すごく教え方が上手なので
Oh, my.
あら　昔はお母さんが引き算教えてあげたのに
I taught him subtraction when he was little,
先生なんて呼ばれちゃって
and now he's become the teacher.
Isn't that right, Kaname-sensei?
ね　要先生
母さんしか呼んでねえっつの
You're the only one who calls me that.
それより　夕飯の買い物行かなくていいのかよ
Don't you need to go shopping for dinner?
Would you like to come with me, Kaname-kun?
じゃ要君も一緒に行こうか
No!
行かねえよ
見りゃ分るんだろう　今勉強してるのよ
Can't you see that I'm studying?
昔は一緒行ってくれたのに
You used to come with me.
What's more important, your mother or your studies?
要君は母さんと勉強どっちが大事なの
Hey, didn't you hear her?
ほら　聞かれてるよ
私と仕事どっちが大事なのって
What's more important, her or your work?
いくら勉強できても女心が分らなくちゃダメだよ　要ち
You can study 'till your eyes bleed, but it won't make a difference if you don't understand girls, Kanamecchi.
She's not a girl! She's my mother!
女心じゃなくて親心だろう
Fine.
分かったわ　勉強のほうが大事なのね　お母さんより
I can tell your studies are more important to you than your own mother.
あーー　泣かせちゃった
You made her cry.
You shouldn't make girls cry!
女子泣かすな
Shut up!
うるせな
もういいから　母さんは出てけよ　邪魔だから
Just get out of here, Mom!
You're in the way!
Sorry.
ごめんね
Oh, how pitiful.
あーー　かわいそう
What are you doing?
なにしてんだよ　早く追い出けろう
Chase after her and tell her you're sorry!
ごめんと言いつつ　あれは恋の駆け引きだよ
It could be the beginning of a beautiful relationship!
She wants you to chase her. Can't you see that?
追いかけてほしくて言ってるんだから　空気読まないと
Enough already!
お前らいい加減にしろ
うめ　スイカ
This watermelon's delicious.
こんなに美味いこいつに塩をぶっかけるなんてこと俺には出来ねえよ
I can't understand why you would ever put salt on something so delicious!
でも僕もそのまま食べるほうが好きだな
I prefer eating them as they are, too.
なんでスイカには塩なんでしょうね
I wonder why people put salt on watermelon...
塩のしょっぱさが余計にスイカを甘く感じさせるんでしょう
The salt makes the watermelon seem even sweeter, doesn't it?
会えない時間が余計にお互いをいとしく感じさせるでしょう
And absence makes the heart grow fonder, doesn't it?
ちげえよ
No, it doesn't.
まぁ　でも　味に飽きたり変化がほしくなったら
I guess I could put salt on it if I got tired of the flavor.
塩振るっつのなんかもありなんかな
うんうん要もお母さんと倦怠期になったら
Yeah. Kaname, when you and your mother get tired of living together...
塩振ったらいいよ　塩
Add salt.
No way!
振るか
もういいから　食い終わったら宿題しろうよ　宿題
Finish your food and do your work!
ごちそうさんでした
Thanks for the food!
All right!
よーし　ジョキーン
I feel like I'm smarter now!
なんか頭よくなった気がする
I can do it!
I know I can do it now!
いける　今の俺ならいけるぜ
やはり病は気から　勉強はメガネから
Illness starts in the mind,
and studying starts with glasses.
要ちもかける
Kanamecchi, do you want some?
Wait, you already have a pair! I'm so stupid!
って　要ちはもうかけてるんじゃん
俺のばか　ばか
I already told you...
だから百金のメガネかけてる暇があったら
If you have time to play with cheap glasses, you might as well do some homework!
一つでも宿題終わらせんか
100 yen stores have everything.
百金っていろんなもんあるよね
Memorization set.
暗記セット
必勝ハチマキ
Victory headband.
Stress ball.
リラックスボール　にぎにぎすると脳が刺激されるって
AnPanda Ball
Squeezing it stimulates your brain.
本当いろんなものがありますね
They really do have everything.
っつか　宿題するのになに余計なもん買ってきてんだよ
Why did you buy all this unnecessary stuff for studying?
いや　ついつい
It kinda just happened.
ねね　要ちメガネいつからかけてんの
Kanamecchi, how long have you been wearing glasses?
Yeah, how long has it been?
そういえば　いつからでしたっけ
Forget about that and study—
そんなことより今は宿題や
You didn't have them in kindergarten.
幼稚園のごろはまだかけてなかったですよね
You were already looking at the world through dark-colored glasses, though.
まぁ　そのころから色メガネで物事を見る子ではあったね
There was that one rainy day, when we were making teru-teru bouzu dolls...
そういえば　雨の日にテルテル坊主作ったことあったけど
I bet you'll draw weird faces on yours.
ぜってえ祐希と悠太は変な顔書くだろう
ひどい　要君は僕らのこと色メガネで見ている
You're so mean.
You're viewing us through dark-colored glasses.
そういうの偏見っていうんだよね
That's called prejudice.
That wasn't prejudicial at all.
あれは全然偏見じゃなかったじゃねえか
とにかく要は生まれた時からメガネとセットだったよ
In any case, you've been wearing glasses since you were born.
好き勝手言うな
Don't say that!
Man, that's awful.
なんだよ　ひどいな　幼馴染のくせに
You're childhood friends, but you forgot when Kanamecchi changed his image.
要ちのチェンジの瞬間忘れたんだかい
We didn't forget. We never remembered it in the first place.
忘れたんじゃなくて　最初から記憶に留めてないだけだよ
そこ胸張って訂正するとこじゃねえだろう
That's nothing to be proud of.
中二のころじゃない　メガネかけたの
Didn't you start wearing glasses in the second year of middle school?
中二　いや　確かあれは
Second year?
No, that was...
塚原君
Tsukahara-kun.
Aren't these yours?
君のだよね
Oh, thank you.
あ　すみません
入学早々理科室に忘れるなんて　いつもかけてたほうがいいんじゃない
I can't believe you lost them so soon after entering middle school.
You should wear them all the time, don't you think?
っつってもな
Yeah, but...
He definitely has coke-bottle glasses.
牛乳瓶の底みたいだったな　あいつのメガネ
Let's call him a nerd next time we see him!
今度からがり勉君って呼ぼうぜ
Yeah, they don't look cool.
やっぱ格好悪いよな
一二三四五六七八九十
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
また負けた　祐希君指相撲強いですよ
I lost again.
Yuuki-kun, you're too good at thumb wrestling.
You're just too weak, Shun.
春が弱すぎなんだよ　次俺左手でやってあげようか
Shall I take you on left-handed?
If you use your left hand,
Shun will have to use his left hand, too.
祐希が左手にしたら自然に春も左手で組むことになっちゃうでしょう
Oh, you're right.
あっ　本当だ
What are you doing?
なにやってんだ　お前ら
Ah, Kaname-kun.
あっ　要君
中学生にもなって指相撲って
Thumb wrestling in middle school?
暇だな
You must have nothing to do.
んなことしてんなら　部活見学でも行ってこいよ
If you have time for that,
let's go check out some clubs.
もうすぐ決めなきゃなんないんだから
We need to decide soon.
ええ　おもしろいですよ　指相撲
But thumb wrestling is fun!
ほら見てください　祐希君が似顔絵書いてくれたんですよ
Here, look at this. Yuuki-kun drew my face!
かわいいですよね
Isn't it cute?
俺のはこの　マンガ読みながらでも倒せるぜっていう余裕ね
This is mine.
He's saying, "I can beat you even while reading manga."
そうそう　祐希すごい指相撲強いんだよ
That's right. Yuuki's really good at thumb wrestling.
そりゃすごいな　中学生活にそれが活かされることがないと思うが
That's great.
I don't think it'll play much of a role in our middle school lives, though.
Kaname, have your eyes gotten worse?
要　もしかして目悪くなった
Huh?
え？　お　まあ
Um, a little.
What?! Really? So that means you can't see the board...
えっ　そうなんですか
じゃ　黒板もよく見えないんじゃ
あ　授業中はメガネかけてるから
Well, I'll wear glasses during class.
Glasses?
メガネ？
要君メガネ買ったんですか
Kaname-kun, you got glasses?
Show us how you look in them.
見せて　メガネかけてるとこ
I wanna see, I wanna see!
みたいです
Are those your glasses? Is that the case?
それメガネ　メガネケース
Hey, hands off!
もう触るな
お前らの前でだけはぜってえかけねえ
I'll never wear them in front of you guys.
You'll laugh at me.
笑うに決まってるからな
春はそんな子じゃないよ
Shun's not like that.
I'm talking about you two!
おめぇらだよ
おめらどうせがり勉だメガネ君だなんだって言うだろうが
I'm sure you'll call me "Nerd" or "Four-eyes."
We wouldn't say that.
いや　そこまでは言わない
かなあ
Or would we?
Why can't you give a clear answer?
なんだその歯切れの悪さは
じゃさあ　俺と勝負しよう　要
Then why don't you thumb wrestle me, Kaname?
俺が勝ったら　メガネかけてるとこ見せてよ
If I win, you'll show us what you look like with your glasses on.
What?
はあ？　なんで俺が指相撲なんか
Why would I--
Sounds good.
いいよ
Hey!
おい
わー　楽しみです
Oh, I'm so excited.
Why'd you answer for me?!
なに勝手に返事してんだよ
It's decided.
はい　手ー　要も親指に顔書いてあげるね
Kaname, I'll draw a face on your thumb, too.
要らねえっつの
I don't need one!
Stop it!
やめろっ
Come on, hold still.
はい　じっとして
If you move, your face will be weird.
動くと変な顔になっちゃうから　もともと変なのに
It's weird enough already.
Matsuoka-kun.
松岡君
Yes?
はい
What are you doing?
さっきからなにしてるの
It looks fun!
なんか楽しそうだよね
指相撲やってるんです
We're thumb wrestling.
Thumb wrestling?
指相撲？
Drawing your face on your thumb is like a traditional part of thumb wrestling.
親指に似顔絵を描くのは指相撲やる時の儀式っていうか
See?
ほら
へえ　かわいい
How cute!
This, too?
これも
That's right.
はい　そうです
Yuuta-kun, do you like drawing?
ね　悠太君って絵描くの好きなの
美術部入るとか
What?
Are you joining the Art Club?
We haven't decided what club we're joining yet.
私たちもまだ部活決めてないんだよね
美術部もいいよね
The Art Club wouldn't be bad.
でも男子バレー部の先輩たちが体育の授業で悠太君見て
Ah, but the upperclassmen in
the Volleyball Club saw Yuuta-kun during PE,
and said they wanted tall guys like him.
あいつみたいに脊高いやつほしいって言ってた
That's Yuuki.
そっち
祐希です
What?
That's Yuuki,
そっちが祐希で　悠太は俺
and I'm Yuuta.
I-I'm so sorry!
ご　ごめんなさい
恥ずかしい
That was embarrassing!
We got them confused!
間違えちゃった
People get the two of you mixed up a lot.
悠太君と祐希君やっぱりよく間違えられちゃいますね
でも二人とも格好いいよね
But they're both so good looking.
本当に似てるよね
They really do look alike.
Well, we're exactly the same, aside from our bangs.
まあ　前髪以外同じだからね
They're identical.
ちょうそっくり
Should I make the eyebrows thicker?
眉毛もっと太くする
メガネは丸メガネ？　銀縁？　牛乳瓶？
Do you want round glasses?
Silver frames?
Coke-bottles?
痛い
What do you mean it's just your bangs? You two are completely different!
どこが前髪以外全部同じだ
全然違うだろう　俺を怒らせる回数だ
You piss me off way more than he does!
You And I
East, Asaba Shoryu.
東　浅羽昇竜
West, Tsukahara.
西　塚原
I don't get a title?
俺がまんまかよ
見合って見合って　はっけよい
Face each other... Ready...
Begin!
のこった
Amazing. What a match!
すごい　いい勝負です
ええ　要も結構強いね
Kaname's pretty good.
なにがマンガ読みながらでも倒せるだよ
You think you can beat me while reading manga?
もらったぜ　この勝負
I've got this one in the bag!
あ　ぶねえな　てめぇ
Watch it!
It wasn't on purpose.
わざとじゃないもん　手が滑っちゃったんだもん
My hand slipped.
Hey, ref!
おい審判　こいつ今犯則しようとしたぞ
He just violated the rules!
You'll have to put your glasses on to protect your eyes, it seems.
目をガードするためにもやっぱメガネかけるしかないね
ですね
Yes.
Why?!
なんでだ
とにかくちゃんと注意しろうよ
Just punish him!
Okay, okay.
祐希　三回ファールしたら失格にするからね
Yuuki, if you foul three times, you lose.
三回あれば十分です　目は二つ
Three's plenty.
He only has two eyes.
Kaname-kun, calm down!
要君　落ち着いてください
Start over.
じゃ　仕切り直しね
ちゃんとやれよな
Play fair this time.
Fine, fine.
分かってるってば
はっけよい　のこった
Ready, fight!
僕　こんな指相撲見たことないです
Look at that!
I've never seen such thumb wrestling.
That wasn't a foul. That was a ten-don.
A what? That doesn't even make sense!
It's gone way beyond thumb wrestling now.
もう指相撲じゃないかね
This sucks.
あー　めんどうくさいな
なんだ　俺に負けるのが悔しくて気合放棄か
What?
Are you resigning because you're afraid you'll lose?
普通に見せてよ　メガネくらい
Just let us see what your glasses look like.
You... Wait!
お前　待て
やめろって
Stop!
I'll just take a peek.
ちょっとだけだよ　ちらっと見るだけ
Ow.
いって　いてな
That hurt.
Apologize, first year.
おい　謝れ　一年
Oh, the glasses.
あー　メガネも
Hey!
おい
すみません
Sorry.
There, there.
I can't believe first years these days.
ったく　最近の一年は
Glasses, glasses.
メガネメガネ　と
ダメだよ　祐希　ちゃんと謝らなんと
What are you doing, Yuuki? You have to apologize.
If you keep acting like that,
they'll have it in for you.
お前生意気な態度取ってと目つけられるぞ
"Have it in for him"?
目つけられるって
あれだよ
You know...
Some older punks will get underclassmen to meet them behind the gym
ヤンキンな上級生が下級生を体育館の裏に呼び出して
and then, they'll beat up the underclassmen.
ぼこぼこにすんだよ
マンガでよくあるんじゃん
It happens all the time in manga.
え？　そうなんですか　怖いです
Really? That's so scary!
大丈夫で　春は
You'll be fine, Shun.
別の意味で呼び出されることはあっても
They might ask you to meet them there for other reasons, though.
Don't do anything dangerous, Yuuki-kun.
むちゃしないでくださいね　祐希君
俺　まあ大丈夫じゃない
Me?
I'll be fine.
Even if something happens,
ほら　もしそうなっても
maybe they'll let me settle it peacefully... with a thumb wrestling match.
指相撲で穏便に済ませてくれるかもしれないし
As if you'd settle something peacefully.
お前が穏便に済まさないだろう
It's oil-based ink.
油性で書きやがって
祐希のやろう　いつか絶対痛い目合わせてやる
One day, Yuuki will get what's coming to him.
Hey, Yuuki...
おい　祐希
Is he in there? I can't see.
いねえのか
よく見えぬ
Hey, do you know...
な　祐希　浅羽祐希は
where Yuuki Asaba is?
Asaba-kun?
浅羽君？
I just saw Asaba-kun heading towards the gym with some third years.
浅羽君ならさっき三年生の人たちと体育館もほうに行ったの見たけど
Third years?
三年生？
Can't be...
まさか
But...
いや　でも
He's going to the gym with some upperclassmen.
上級生と体育館なら
This could be...
もしかしなくても　これって
This could be bad!
やべえじゃん
It's his own fault that he doesn't have any manners.
そもそもあいつは根っから礼儀っつか　常識が足りなさすぎんだよ
It serves him right. Right.
たまにはいい薬だ　いい薬
Yuuta! Shun!
悠太　春
要君どうしたんですか
Kaname-kun, what's wrong?
Yuuki was...
祐希が　祐希が
Yuuki was dragged off behind the gym!
体育館裏につれてかれた
What?
It's probably because he refused to apologize when he bumped into them yesterday.
きっと昨日ぶつかっても謝らなかったからだ
早く体育館裏行って
Let's go to the gym and...
No, it's fine.
いや　大丈夫じゃ
なに言ってんだよ　お前心配じゃねえのかよ
What are you talking about?
Aren't you worried?
このままじゃ祐希三年のやつらにぼこぼこにされんだぞ
If we don't do something, Yuuki's gonna get beat up by some third years!
お前それでも祐希の兄貴かよ
Can you call yourself Yuuki's...
Well, we don't know if he's been beaten up yet.
や　ぼこぼこってまだ決まったわけじゃねえけど
とにかく立てて　ほら
Just stand up. Come on.
あれ　みんなでなにしてるの
Huh? What are you all doing?
Like I said, Yuuki's gonna...
だから祐希が
Huh?
え？　悠太
Yuu... ta?
Yeah.
そうだけど
Huh?
Some guys from the Volleyball Club forced me to go to the gym to watch them play.
さきさ　男子バレー部の人たちに
見学だけでも来てくれて
無理やり体育館につれてかれて
もう大変だったんよ　とりあえず
It was a hassle, but I went anyway.
Why...?
なんで　体育館って
The gym? Then...
One, two, three, four, five,
一二三四五六七八九十
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
俺の勝ちですね　要君
I win, Kaname-kun.
So, what happened to Yuuki?
で　祐希がなんだって
なんだ　なんでもねえ　なんでもねえ　なんでもねえ
Nothing, nothing, nothing at all!
Shun, you should have told me!
春　途中で教えろうよ
I was going to, but you seemed so desperate.
言おうと思ったんですよ　でもなんか要君すごく必死だったから
必死　じゃねえ
I wasn't...
Yuuta, what am I going to do?
悠太　どうしよう　すごい寒い　要が俺のこと超心配
Kaname was so worried about—
Don't say it!
言うな
あれ　要君　それ
Kaname-kun, are those...
え　指相撲負けたからって　本当にかけてきてくれるなんて思わなかったです
I know you lost at thumb wrestling,
but I didn't think you'd actually wear them.
Nothing good comes from not being able to see.
ちゃんと見えてないと　ろくなことにならねえからな
いいんじゃない　お似合いだよ
Not bad. They look good on you.
Why does that sound condescending coming from you?
おめぇが言うと なんでこう悪意を感じるだろうな
Hey! What are you drawing?
おい
なに勝手に描いてんだよ
They really do look good on you.
でも
本当に似合いますよ
いいよ
You don't have to say that.
無理して言わなくても
Kaname-kun, you look really good in glasses.
要君
メガネすごく似合ってます
Finished.
はい　完成
You used oil-based ink again!
また油性で描いただろう
Who cares?
いいじゃん　これからもずっとかけてるんだからさ
You'll be wearing glasses from now on,
要がね君
Kaname-lens-kun.
What's Kaname-lens?!
なんだ　要がねって
Whoops, I remembered something I shouldn't have.
いかん　要らんことまで思い出した
この恥は墓場まで持っていこう
I'll carry that shame to my grave.
で　結局いつメガネかけてたの　中二
So, how long have you had glasses?
Since second year of middle school?
Yeah, my second year of middle school.
はい　中二だ　中二
中一じゃなかったでしたっけ　要がね君
Wasn't it our first year...
Kaname-lens-kun?
What? What's a Kaname-lens-kun?
えー　なになに　要がねって
You...
いや　それがさ　要が俺のこと超心配して
Well, Kaname was really worried about me...
言うな
Don't say it!
あ　茉咲ちゃん
Masaki-chan!
Do I look weird?
やっぱり変ですか
...suits you.
似合ってるわ
Huh?
It really suits you!
すごく似合ってる
Really? That's good.
そうですか　よかった
Sorry.
ごめんなさい
You Have One New Message
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
It's from Chizuru-kun.
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
Hey there, Shun-chan! I'm sending
lllyou this pic Kanamecchi took of
..llus. ヽ(･∀･)ﾉ
....lThat watermelon was super
__lllldelicious!
Chizuru-kun
Hey there~
千鶴君からだ
HHHHHHHHHH
HHHHHHHHHHH
I got my hair cut in the garden at Kaname-kun's house.
要君の庭の中で髪切ったんですよ
Really?
へえ
I got my hair cut, but it didn't help with the heat as much as I expected.
髪切ったけど　思ったほど涼しくならなかったですね
行きましょうか
Shall we go?
Yeah!
Among the sunset's clouds and occasional breeze,
それでも　夕焼けの雲と時より吹く風に
僕は夏の終わりの気配を感じた
I could feel the summer ending.
Glasses and Et cetera
僕は泣き虫で　悔しくて
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
だけどあなたに今伝えたいんだ
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
ただまっすぐに僕を見つめる
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
強くて優しいその瞳に応えるために
Giving me the chance to answer you and the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
いつしか見失ってた
一番大切なものも
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
そっとあなたが教えてくれた
たしかにそう思えるから
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
僕は弱虫で　嫌だった
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta n dakedo
I hated how weak I was
だけどもっともっと強くなるから
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
あなたのことを守れるような僕になるから
anata no koto mo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you and me both
だから　少し待ってて
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
"Next time: Next to an Apple."
Next to an Apple